worldoftrade.com 2015-03-26

# Privacy Policy

  * Privacy and data protection policy
    * World of Trade FZCO (´we´ or ´us´) operate the website at [www.worldoftrade.com]() (the ´website´). You can contact us with any questions you may have relating to the website by visiting the following URL: http://www.worldoftrade.com/contact-us.htm.
    * Your right to privacy is important to us. The following terms are provided to explain how we collect and use information about you so that you can make an informed choice about using the website. Your disclosure to us of your personal information will be an indication that you have read these terms and consent to our use of your personal information in accordance with these terms. Please check this Privacy Policy regularly as changes will be posted here.
    * We will hold your personal data securely in accordance with all relevant privacy and data protection laws and regulations applicable to us.
    * Personal data is not stored nor captured through the website without your prior knowledge and consent. Where personal information is captured (e.g. through web-based forms for feedback, registration, requests, etc), you will be informed as to what personal information is being collected, who will use it, and for what purpose(s) it will be used.
    * The only personal information that we will collect is the personal information that you provide (see paragraph [2] below for details of other information we collect on the website, from which we cannot identify any personal information). Any personal information that you do provide will only be used for the purposes for which you have provided it and it will only be used by us or our appointed agents/contractors for carrying out the purpose for which the information is provided.
    * Although we will make every effort to ensure your personal information is not disclosed to any third party without your consent, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information in response to a court order, threat of legal action, or approach from any government authority, relating to an allegation that you have used the website in breach of this Agreement or an allegation of any other unlawful activity by you in connection with, or arising out of your use of, the website.
    * You may at any time ask us to amend or remove your personal details from our records or our mailing lists relating to this website by sending an e-mail to tech.support@worldoftrade.com. Should you request that we amend or suppress records containing your personal data, we will endeavour to do so as promptly as practical. However, where you ask to be removed from a mailing list, you may still receive communications for some time while we process your request.
  * IP addresses and cookies
    * We may collect information about your computer, including your IP address, operating system and browser type for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users´ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
    * For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general Internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer´s hard drive. They help us to improve our website and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us to:
      * estimate our audience size and usage pattern;
      * store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests;
      * speed up your searches; and
      * Recognise you when you return to our website.
    * You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our website.
    * Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.
